James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1982-2010; 4
  - 81st Session, 2007-2010; 8
    - Senate Bills, 2009; 3
      - SB 519, Paternity, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - SB 519, Committee Report, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - SB 519, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - SB 519, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - SB 876, Soil Testing, General, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - SB 876, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - SB 876, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - SB 876, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - SB 876, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - SB 1145, Folding State Flag, General, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - SB 1145, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - SB 1145, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - SB 1145, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - SB 1145, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - SB 1694, County Courthouse, General, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - SB 1694, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - SB 1694, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - SB 1694, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - SB 2513, McLennan- Groundwater, General, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - SB 2513, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - SB 2513, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - SB 2513, Committee Report, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - SB 2513, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - SB 2513, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Joint Resolutions, 2009; 4
      - Joint Resolution Draft, Constitutional Amendment For The Vote Required To Be Elected Governor, circa 2009 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Joint Resolution Draft, Exemption Of Ad Valorem Taxation By A School District, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - Joint Resolution Draft, Recognizing Bad Precedents as the Official Band of 81st Session, circa 2009 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Commemoratives and Commendations, 2009; 5
      - Hodde, Calvin, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - HR 1383, Governor Secession, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      - HR 1467, Bob Bullock Scholars Program Of Baylor University, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - HR 2872, Reed, Alexander Christian, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 32)
      - NAVA 42 Flag Presentation Certificate for Jon Radel, 2009 July 24 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Topical, 2009-2010; 6
      - The American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 (Box 57, Folder 34)
      - Trans-Texas Corridor 35, 2010 April 26 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Committees, 1996-2010; 9
    - Anti-Crime Committee, 2002; 1
      - General, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - Bosque River Advisory Committee (BRAC), 1996-2000; 2
      - General, undated (Box 57, Folder 37)
      - Activities, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 38)
      - Briefing Papers, 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 39)
      - Dairy Farm Inspections, 2000 October (Box 57, Folder 40)
      - Goals and Rules, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 41)
      - Members, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 42)
      - Memos and Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 57, Folder 43)
      - Minutes, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Civil Practices, 2000, undated; 3
      - Hearing, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 45)
      - Study Groups, undated (Box 57, Folder 46)
      - Subcommittee On Judicial Interpretations Of Law, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Calendars, 2009; 4
      - Minutes, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Insurance, 2001; 5
      - General, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Jurisprudence, 1998-2009; 6
      - General, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Driving Under Influence, 2001 March (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 March 4 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 March 25 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 April 1 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 April 15 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee On Violent Crime, Public Hearing, 2009 March 17 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - 76th Session Interim Report, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - 76th Session Legislation Summary, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Higher Education, 1996-2000; 7
      - General, 1996-1998 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Grants, 2000, undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Hopwood Decision, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Judiciary and Civil Jurisprudence, 2009; 8
      - 81st Session Bills, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Public Education, 2009, undated; 9
      - 81st Session Bills, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - House Public Ed Marathon T-Shirt, undated (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Public Health, 2009; 10
      - General, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - HB 1358, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 March 17 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 April 9 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - 81st Session Bills, 2009 March (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - State Affairs, 2009, undated; 11
      - 81st Session Bills, 2009 March (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Notes, undated (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Supreme Court Advisory, 1998-2002; 12
      - General, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Appointment Response Letters, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - Decisions and Recommendations, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Fleming Foods of Texas v. Comptroller Rylander and Attorney General Cornyn, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Agenda, 2000 January (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Proposed Uniform Court Rules for Coverage of Judicial Proceeding in Texas Trial and Appellate Courts, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Report of the Special Subcommittee on Implementations of Family Code, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Rules Advisory, 1998-2000 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Rules of Discovery, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Select Committee on Judicial Interpretation of the Laws, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Texas Rules of Appellate Procedure, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Texas Rules of Civil Procedure, 1998-2000 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Technology Economic Development and Workforce, 2009; 13
      - Public Hearing, 2009 April 6 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Public Hearing, 2009 April 22 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Ways and Means, 2009; 14
      - 81st Session Bills, 2009 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Democratic Caucus, 2003-2010, undated; 10
    - General, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Caucus Survey, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Democratic Policy Committee Agenda, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - District Analysis, undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Draft of Texas Democratic Convention Agenda, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Dunnam Proposal to Form Ad-Hoc Committee on Gambling in Texas, 2010 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - House Democratic Caucus Staff, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Member Lists, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Member Issue Priorities, circa 2003 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Memorandum on House Democratic Campaign Committee, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - News Clips about Speaker Craddick, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Other States, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Retama Horse Track Gambling in Selma, TX, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Staff Briefings, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - “Straight Deal for Texas” Report From Caucus Task Force on Ethics and Government Integrity, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Texas Blueprint Working Timeline Roll-Out, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Memos, 1998-2010, undated; 11
    - General, 1998-2010, undated; 1
      - General, 1998 January (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - General, 1998 February (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - General, 1998 May (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - General, 1998 June (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - General, 1998 July (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - General, 1998 August (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - General, 1998 September (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - General, 1998 October (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - General, 1998 November (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - General, 1998 December (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - General, 1999 January (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - General, 1999 February (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - General, 1999 March (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - General, 1999 April (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - General, 1999 May (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - General, 1999 June (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - General, 1999 July (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - General, 1999 August (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - General, 2000 January (Box 60, Folder 29)
      - General, 2000 April (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - General, 2000 May (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - General, 2000 July (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - General, 2000 August (Box 60, Folder 33)
      - General, 2000 September (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - General, 2000 December (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - General, 2001 January (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - General, 2001 February (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - General, 2001 March (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - General, 2001 April (Box 60, Folder 39)
      - General, 2001 May (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - General, 2001 June (Box 60, Folder 41)
      - General, 2001 November (Box 60, Folder 42)
      - General, 2002 April (Box 60, Folder 43)
      - General, 2002 May (Box 60, Folder 44)
      - General, 2003 July (Box 60, Folder 45)
      - General, 2003 October (Box 60, Folder 46)
      - General, 2005 May (Box 60, Folder 47)
      - General, 2002-2006 (Box 60, Folder 48)
      - Democratic Caucus, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 49)
      - Open Records Request for House Business Office, 2010 May 18 (Box 60, Folder 50)
      - Sportsman’s Caucus Election, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 51)
      - Sunset Recommendations on Workers’ Compensation, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 52)
      - Teacher Health Issue, 2002 April (Box 60, Folder 53)
      - 79th Session, Speaker of the House Pledge, 2004 November (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - "Monday Memos", 2003; 2
      - “Monday Memos”, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 55)
  - Topical, 1982-2007; 12
    - Ardmore (Killer Ds), 2003, undated; 1
      - Department of Public Safety, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 56)
      - Dunnam Guest Column, 2003 May (Box 60, Folder 57)
      - Killer Ds T-Shirt, 2003 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 10)
      - Negative Constituent Correspondence (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 60, Folder 58)
      - Negative Constituent Correspondence (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 60, Folder 59)
      - News Clippings, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 60)
      - Other State Positive Correspondence, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 61)
      - Positive Constituent Correspondence (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Positive Constituent Correspondence (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Positive Constituent Correspondence (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Redistricting Press Release, 2003 May (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Report of Expenditures, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Republican Talking Points, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Walkout Letters, 2003 May (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Bosque River, 1982-2004; 2
      - General, c. 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Big Creek (Tri-County) Watershed Project Map, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Brazos Valley Groundwater Conservation District, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Bosque Watershed Paired Stream Assessment, 2001 April 17 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Bosque River/Lake Waco Legislation, undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Concentrated Animal Feeding Operation (CAFO), 1990-2002 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - EPA 319 Grant, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Hidden View Dairy, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Lake Waco Water Quality, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Leon River and Leon Creek, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - News Clippings, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - North Bosque River Watershed, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Permit to Authorize Discharges of Wastewater Associated with Livestock Manure Compost Operations, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Public Interest Sunset Working Group, undated (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Texas Natural Resources Conservation Commission (TNRCC), 1999-2002 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Texas Natural Resources Conservation Commission Compliance History, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Texas Natural Resources Conservation Commission, Permit Reconsiderations, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Texas Natural Resource Conservation Commission Proposed General Permit, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Texas Natural Resources Conservation Commission v. Texas Association of Dairymen, circa 2001 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Texas State Soil and Water Conservation Board (TSSWCB), 2004 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Texas Water Code, circa 2000 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Texas Water Development Board, 2001 March (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Total Maximum Daily Loads (TMDL), 1999-2001 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Total Maximum Daily Loads (TMDL), 1999-2002 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Charter Schools, 1995-2004, undated; 3
      - General (1 of 3), 2001-2002, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - General (2 of 3), 2001-2002, undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - General (3 of 3), 2001-2002, undated (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Accountability Rating System, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Agendas, Subcommittee on Charter Schools, 2000 June-August (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Application, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Bills, Preliminary Drafts, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 100, Charters, 2002 March (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Charter Meeting, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Charter School Board Training, 2002 February-April (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Committee on Public Education Report, 2000 December (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 1 (1 of 3), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 1 (2 of 3), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 1 (3 of 3), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 2 (1 of 4), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 2 (2 of 4), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 2 (3 of 4), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 2 (4 of 4), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 3 (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Committee Transcript, Tape 3 (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Comparison of Charter School Legislation, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Contract for Charter, 1996, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Dallas City Code, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Executive Summary, "Broken Promises: Charter Schools in Texas", 2000 September (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Funding, 1997-2002 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Grade 3 Reading TAAS, 2000-2002 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Hearing Questions, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - HB 6, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - HB 6, Media, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - History of Actions on Charter Schools, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - House Committee on Public Education, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Houston Annenberg Challenge, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Knowledge is Power Program, 2000 Testing Results (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Laws and Rules, Charter Laws, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Laws and Rules, Summary of Charter Laws, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Laws and Rules, TEA Charter Rules, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Linking Conditions and Practices to Student Achievement, 2002 April (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Mission or Philosophy Statements, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - National Study of Charter Schools Report, 2001 June (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Nepotism, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - News Clippings, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - News Clippings and Articles, 2001-2002 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - No Child Left Behind, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Notebook, Agenda for Public Hearing, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Notebook, Amendments to Oppose Private School Vouchers, Generic, undated (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Notebook, Amendments to Oppose Private School Vouchers, HB 2465, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Notebook, Annual Number of Charters, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Notebook, Charter Amendments Requests Addition of Campuses/Sites, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Notebook, Charter Campus Enrollment, Rating, and Function, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Notebook, Charter School Management Companies, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Notebook, Charter School Monitors, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Notebook, Charter Sponsoring Entity Information Report, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Notebook, Interim Charge for Subcommittee, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Notebook, History of Actions on Charter Schools, 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Notebook, Number of Applications and Charters Granted by Generation, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Notebook, Side-by-Side Comparison: HB 6, 77th Legislature, and Implementing Rules, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Notebook, Texas Education Agency, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Notebook, Texas Open-Enrollment Charter School Third-Year Evaluation Report, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Notebook, Timeline of Activities and Products Supporting Implementation of HB 6, 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Notebook, Performance of Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Notes, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Open-Enrollment Charter Guidelines, 1995 October 13 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Open-Enrollment Charter Guidelines and Application, 1999 November 5 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Open-Enrollment Third Year Evaluation, 2000 March (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Parent, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Press Releases, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases and Testimonies, 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - Public Education Sub-Committee on Charter Schools, 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - Recommendations and Reviews, 1999-2001 (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - Reports, 1998-2002 (Box 65, Folder 25)
      - A Review of Charter Schools in Texas, 1995-1999 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - A Review of Charter Schools in Texas, 2000 September (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - A Review of Charter Schools in Texas, 2000 October (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Statistics, 2000-2002 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Sub-committee Agenda and Assignments, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Superintendent Salaries, 2001-2002 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Sunset Advisory Commission, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Testimonies, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Testimonies, Subcommittee on Charter Schools, 2000 June (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Testimonies, Subcommittee on Charter Schools, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Texas Education Agency, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, Third-Year Evaluation Part One, 2000 March (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, Third-Year Evaluation School Profiles, 2000 March (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, Third-Year Evaluation, 2000 July (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools Fourth-Year Evaluation, 2001 January (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, Fourth-Year Evaluation, 2001 June (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, Fourth-Year Evaluation, 2001 September (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools Fifth-Year Evaluation, 2002 June (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools Fifth-Year Evaluation, Summary Tables, 2002 June (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools Fifth-Year Evaluation (1 of 2), 2002 July (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Texas Open-Enrollment Charter Schools Fifth-Year Evaluation (2 of 2), 2002 July (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - The Eagle Project, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Virtual Schools, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Redistricting, 1997-2006, undated; 4
      - General, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Amendments, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - General Arguments, 2002-2003 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Congressional Redistricting of East Rural Texas, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Current Districts, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - District 23 Map and Information, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Editorials, Abilene Reporter News, 2003 May-July (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Editorials, Amarillo Globe-News, 2003 August-September (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Editorials, Austin American Statesman, 2003 February-September (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Editorials, Beaumont Enterprise, 2003 August 11-13 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Editorials, Bryan-College Station Eagle, 2003 August 15 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Editorials, Corpus Christi Caller Times, 2003 May-September (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Editorials, Dallas Morning News, 2003 January-September (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Editorials, El Paso Times, 2003 July-September (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Editorials, Fort Worth Star Telegram, 2003 January-September (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Editorials, Houston Chronicle, 2003 February-September (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Editorials, Longview News Journal, 2003 May-September (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Editorials, Lubbock Avalanche Journal, 2003 July-September (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Editorials, Lufkin Daily News, 2003 September 11-14 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Editorials, The Monitor, 2003 July-August (Box 67, Folder 27)
      - Editorials, Park City People, circa. 2003 (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - Editorials, San Angelo Standard Times, 2003 July-September (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Editorials, San Antonio Express News, 2003 March-September (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Editorials, Waco Tribune-Herald, 2003 May-September (Box 67, Folder 31)
      - Editorials, Wichita Falls Times Record News, 2003 August 15 (Box 67, Folder 32)
      - HB 3, Conference Committee Report, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 33)
      - HB 3, Floor Packet Speaking Points, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - HB 2254 Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, General, 2000-2001 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Hearings, 1999-2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Maps, State House Districts 56 and 57, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Maps, State House Districts McLennan County, 2000 September 8 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Maps, State Senate District 22, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Maps, U.S. Congressional Districts, 2001 July-August (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, McLennan County, 2001-2002 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Population, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - House Committee on Redistricting, Redistricting Software, 2000-2001 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - House Journal Partially Signed by Members (51 copies), 2003 May 12 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - League of United Latin American Citizens v. Perry Opinion, 2006 June 28 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Memos and Press Releases, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - News Clippings, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Notes and Correspondence, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Opposition, Abuse of Power, circa 2003 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Opposition, Texans Say NO, circa 2003 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Opposition, Unprecedented, circa 2002-2003 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Proposed State House District 56 Maps, undated (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Questions for House Floor Debate, circa 2003 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Redistricting Unity Beer Bottle, undated (Box 81 OVZ, Folder 4)
      - Statement, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Statistics, 2002-2003 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Talking Points, Minorities, circa 2002-2003 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Talking Points, Priorities, circa 2003 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Talking Points, Rural, circa 2003 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Texas Legislative Council News, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 2)